export const set2 = [
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  62</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  29</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["90", "91", "92", "89"],
    answer: "91"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  65</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  45</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["112", "109", "110", "108"],
    answer: "110"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  25</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  82</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["108", "106", "105", "107"],
    answer: "107"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  98</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  34</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["132", "130", "131", "133"],
    answer: "132"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  66</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  39</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["103", "106", "105", "104"],
    answer: "105"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  65</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  68</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["132", "134", "133", "131"],
    answer: "133"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  45</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  42</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["86", "87", "88", "85"],
    answer: "87"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  38</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  56</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["93", "95", "94", "92"],
    answer: "94"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  94</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  63</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["158", "157", "156", "155"],
    answer: "157"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  54</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  24</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["78", "77", "79", "76"],
    answer: "78"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  54</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  36</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["91", "89", "90", "88"],
    answer: "90"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  37</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  21</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["57", "58", "59", "56"],
    answer: "58"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  27</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  63</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["89", "91", "90", "88"],
    answer: "90"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  68</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  24</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["91", "93", "92", "90"],
    answer: "92"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  64</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  39</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["102", "104", "103", "101"],
    answer: "103"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  44</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  19</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    output: ["64", "62", "63", "61"],
    answer: "63"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  42</div>
          <div class="user-row"><span class="op">+</span>  37</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["78", "80", "79", "77"],
    answer: "79"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  36</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  43</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["80", "78", "77", "79"],
    answer: "79"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  19</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  54</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["72", "74", "73", "71"],
    answer: "73"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  45</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  48</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["94", "92", "93", "91"],
    answer: "93"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  89</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  58</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["146", "148", "147", "145"],
    answer: "147"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  43</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  23</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["67", "65", "66", "64"],
    answer: "66"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  62</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  23</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["84", "86", "85", "83"],
    answer: "85"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  55</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  22</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["76", "78", "77", "75"],
    answer: "77"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  49</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  24</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["74", "72", "73", "71"],
    answer: "73"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  57</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  34</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["90", "92", "91", "89"],
    answer: "91"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  46</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  63</div>
          <div'installer class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["108", "110", "109", "107"],
    answer: "109"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  52</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  55</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["107", "106", "108", "105"],
    answer: "107"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  95</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  43</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["137", "139", "138", "136"],
    answer: "138"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  46</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  45</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["90", "92", "91", "89"],
    answer: "91"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  46</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  33</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["79", "78", "80", "77"],
    answer: "79"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  36</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  73</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["108", "110", "109", "107"],
    answer: "109"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  29</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  62</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["90", "92", "91", "89"],
    answer: "91"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  72</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  24</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["95", "97", "96", "94"],
    answer: "96"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  35</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  24</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["58", "60", "59", "57"],
    answer: "59"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  35</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  23</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["57", "59", "58", "56"],
    answer: "58"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  86</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  49</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["134", "136", "135", "133"],
    answer: "135"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  88</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  61</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["148", "150", "149", "147"],
    answer: "149"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  29</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  44</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["72", "74", "73", "71"],
    answer: "73"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  62</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  34</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["95", "97", "96", "94"],
    answer: "96"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row"> 344</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span> 976</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["1319", "1321", "1320", "1318"],
    answer: "1320"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row"> 965</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span> 829</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["1793", "1795", "1794", "1792"],
    answer: "1794"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row"> 345</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span> 486</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["830", "832", "831", "829"],
    answer: "831"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row"> 268</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span> 636</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["903", "905", "904", "902"],
    answer: "904"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row"> 476</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span> 549</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["1024", "1026", "1025", "1023"],
    answer: "1025"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row"> 739</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span> 685</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["1423", "1425", "1424", "1422"],
    answer: "1424"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row"> 797</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span> 669</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["1465", "1467", "1466", "1464"],
    answer: "1466"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row"> 288</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span> 992</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["1279", "1281", "1280", "1278"],
    answer: "1280"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row"> 549</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span> 639</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["1187", "1189", "1188", "1186"],
    answer: "1188"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row"> 742</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span> 954</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["1695", "1697", "1696", "1694"],
    answer: "1696"
  }
];